Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/thanh-dinh-nguyen-069651259 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Project Governance
Manufacturing Operations
Management
Stakeholder Analysis

Thanh Dinh Nguyen

Project Manager at Suntory PepsiCo Vietnam Beverage Tân Bình, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Over 10 years working in project management, 2 years in packaging development, 2 years in the digital conversion project management, Green Field, Brown Field, MEP, Soft drink technology, Beverage &Food processing, water treatment, food & soft drink production lines, new factories, utilities...

Experience

Suntory PepsiCo Vietnam Beverage 13 years 11 months

Project Manager May 2011 - Present (13 years 11 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Packaging Development Specialist September 2017 - October 2019 (2 years 2 months) Vietnam

develop new packaging primiry, secondary packaging

Spvb

Project Manager for Digitalization January 2022 - June 2024 (2 years 6 months) Vietnam

Digitalization in Manufacture (Barcode, EHS, Gemba, SOP, Security, Capa, PMS, ...)

SPVB

Packaging Specialist September 2017 - October 2019 (2 years 2 months) Vietnam

packaging development, incl. Pet bottle, preform, CAN, Closures, Lid, carton, film, labeling, pallet...

Page 1 of 2

Education

Danang University of Science and Technology
Bachelor of Applied Science - BASc · (September 2004 - June 2009)

Danang University of Science and Technology Engineer's degree, Mechanical Engineering · (2004 - 2009)